Now you just pretend you hadn't talked to me any before, and you tell me about the government moving you up here.
Well, now, I don't remember the day or the month or nothing like that, you understand?
But I know they come one evening, and I just was fixing to quit working in my garden.
And he comes and he says, well, says, is this Miss Davis?
And I said, that's what they call me.
other words ain't loose, I suggest. He says, well, I'm taking pictures around, says the
government's gonna take over everything and Gainesville's gonna have to move out. I said, all this many years? I said, you talk crazy.
And he's like, he says, no. Says, I'm here just to tell you. He says, put me to work.
And he says, uh, then my chickens was all out and it was late in the evening, you know.
I told him, I says, well you'll have to excuse me, I got to put my chickens in the chicken yard.
He says, that's just what I want you to do.
Well, there was a shark fellow with him, you know.
But he didn't ever tell me who he was, you understand?
And I went to put my chickens in the chicken yard.
and fed them, and I had on my old bonnet and shirt where I'd been working, you know, and I
throwed the corn out, and I noticed this short feller walked up close to him and said something
I noticed, and he said, well, you've got a pretty bunch of chickens, says, do they lay?
I says, yes. I said, sometimes I pick up nine eggs a day and sometimes I don't.
He said, well, this sure is a pretty fellow.
Well, I didn't know this shark man walked up to him and took my picture just as I went
to throw some corn out to him, you know.